This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever!
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop!
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far!
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home!
I'm so
truly grateful!
I ran into you on that day so long ago!
We laughed every moment
with tears in our eyes!
Till we knew we weren't alone!
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way!
And with it I know we'll rise!
We'll be flying up high!
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you wanna fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
I don't matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting
plans, we'll reach it.
We are home from the horizon
out on the edge of the world.
If there is a place that
I want to take you to?
Let's head for it then!
But as for the way we already know.
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice.
That can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated.
It crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I swear.
I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer together.
I'm telling you in our path.
I trust that it will lead us.
To another sea untarded.
Cause now we are home.
On the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
There is a place that
I want to take you to.
Let's head for it then.
But after the way, we already know.
We promised it long ago.
I'll send you to the far
ends of the new world!
The G-G-Cannonball!
No more biscuits!
Oh, my God.
Excuse me, Mama.
Sweet General Smoothie has arrived!
Um... Wonderful!
Sweet General Katakuri should be
arriving any moment now as well!
Lovely!
This will be a real treat!
It's been ages since
everyone got together.
Uh, what about Cracker?
Shouldn't he be back home by now?
Soon, I'm sure, and with
Straw Hat's head is a gift!
Goodness, I can't wait!
Huh?
Well, that's weird.
What happened?
What is it?
Big brother!
Look at this!
He's in terrible shape!
This is messed up.
Cracker's one of our sweet three generals.
I'm gonna kill whoever did this to him.
Where's the bastard?
Seems he came flying from pretty far away.
Must have been the seducing woods.
He was supposed to take care
of Straw Hat Luffy there.
Then you know what that means.
Straw Hat Luffy is still at large.
He's around here somewhere.
Put out an emergency alert!
We need to take shelter now! What? Why?
Sweet General Cracker got
beat by Straw Hat! No way!
Hey, are you alright?
That was insane.
I ate a lifetime's worth of biscuits.
Huh, looks like you're shrinking already.
Uh-huh, that's because fourth
gear uses a lot of energy.
So there you are.
Were you hiding in the bushes? Kind of.
I ran away so Cracker wouldn't murder me.
I thought you guys were
going to lose for sure.
They're blunt, don't you think?
Well, I mean, he's one of
the sweet three generals.
Well, it's fine.
That was scary, but... We won!
Woo!
Huh?
Would I kill you guys to cheer?
We'd be one of Big Mom's
top fighters, after all!
I...
I can't even move.
We've engaged in treachery most foul.
We helped the enemy, and now
General Cracker has lost.
Everyone in Totoland knows that Mama's
vivacard holds tremendous
power over us homies.
That's why she doesn't share
pieces of it to anyone anymore,
not even to the little
Sprouts in her own family.
So why do you have one? Oh, neat.
This thing is even more
valuable than I thought.
Listen, you're in much
worse trouble than before.
And why's that?
A while back, Sweet General
Snack got taken down, too.
Then Cracker's fleet painted the
sea black with their numbers,
and Linlin's fury summoned the storm.
The enemy ships, powerful as they were,
got torn to shreds in the blink of an eye.
A storm?
Linlin can command the
weather, quite literally.
She controls weather?
In her left hand, Zeus, a thunder cloud.
In her right hand,
Prometheus, a living sun.
Once her rage is awakened, there's
nothing in this world that can stop her.
In other words,
you better get the heck out of here before
she finds out what you did to her boy.
She can get as mad as
she wants. I don't care.
I'm the one who should be angry here.
I still can't get over what Saji did.
How could he leave without telling us why?
All we got was a dumb note.
It's my problem to solve.
I'll be back soon.
So give everybody my best.
Okay, we only made it this far.
Thanks to Pudding's map,
and we already lost Peckums.
We should have Sanji by now,
but nobody showed at the coast.
We don't know if it was a trap or
if something bad happened to them.
Then we got lost in the
forest, wasted time, fighting.
Once Sanji gets married, he'll
be part of Big Mom's crew,
and it'll be too late to help.
That means we gotta get moving.
Yeah, but when is the wedding?
Cracker said the Vinsmokes were headed
to some castle for the ceremony,
and that should be today.
It's still morning.
We might have enough time to stop them.
Time isn't the issue.
If you don't run away, you'll die.
Don't worry. Let's go!
Hey, Tree! Huh?
You know where the castle
is, don't you? I suppose.
Good, I need you to carry me there.
Nein, I refuse.
I won't quit. No way.
We're taking Soji back.
It's chopper.
How are you doing? Hanging in there.
We should be able to meet up with you
and Brooke if everything works out.
It doesn't sound like things
are working out at all.
You can't help us from outside the
mirror, so it's better not to worry.
Just keep going for...
Hey, Chopper!
Seriously, Nabi, everything's fine.
We're doing right over here.
Oh, everything's fine, huh?
At any rate, we'll keep heading to
the castle and hope we run into Sanji.
Sounds good.
Once you rescue him, use that
piece of the mirror to contact us.
It broke!
Hey, Chopper? Carrot?
It's a normal mirror now.
Oh, I hope they're okay.
Ah!
He's shrinking down already?
Whoa! What?
He's freaking me out!
No way!
I can't believe it!
He's almost back to normal!
The human body doesn't work like that!
Gimme meat! Meat?
Hey there, Fraulein!
You've got good luck. Why's that?
There they are.
That's German double six.
So is Sanji with them?
Yeah, look!
Hey! Sanji!
Your Majesty, something
is charging towards us.
That idiot, he made it all
the way to whole cake island.
And what's with that tree?
It's running.
Hey, sanji!
We finally made it—I was
afraid we'd be too late.
But it looks like we're right on time.
What are they doing here?
This is bad—how amusing!
how amusing That's Straw Hat Luffy.
Hey!
He came here to pick you up!
You're gonna tip over
the calicoat, you maniac!
Come on, Sanji!
You said you'd be back,
but I didn't want to wait.
You know me.
Let's party!
I was gonna come alone, but
it turned into a whole thing.
You mentioned your hands
are important to you.
If you try to flee, your
hands will be blown off.
You know what happens
if you know Sholeiloh.
Zoro took a team and
headed to the land of Wano.
I won't hesitate to relieve
this man of his head.
So it's me, Brook, Nami, and
Chopper who came to get you.
You'll be a sacrifice for
the family, understood?
I haven't changed my opinion of you.
But as a man, if you ever
stray from the honorable path,
then I'll slit my own throat.
Sanji! I'm hungry!
And I do not think of you as a worthy son.
Because as a parent, I've
got to take responsibility.
Loving you as a son is my greatest shame.
Hey, Sanji.
Take care.
Don't catch cold.
I'll explain more back on the boat.
Sanji!
What the heck's gotten into you?
Leave my sight, bunch
of low-class pirates.
Make no mistake, I have
always been a Vinsmoke.
Which makes me a prince.
Of the Germa kingdom.
I kept all this a secret from you because,
knowing this would make
things harder for you.
But now that it's out, you can see there's
a clear difference in our standings.
If I stay here, I'll
have all the servants,
soldiers, and riches
I could ever dream of!
So I can go back to that crappy ship with
you and your friends
on some dumb adventure!
Or I can stay right here
and marry the beautiful
daughter of a wealthy
and powerful emperor.
Now, which of those do you
think would make me happier?
Here, I'll spell it out.
I just wrote that note
to get you off my back.
I'm not going anywhere.
It's noble of you to come all the way
here to get me, but you wasted your time.
I'm not leaving.
I've already forgotten your name.
Yeah, whatever!
You big liar!
Think I'm gonna buy
that don't worry Sanji.
I'll help you drive them off.
Don't you dare
This one's mine.
I'll send him packing
What do you mean you'll send me packing
I want you to leave what else can I mean
Don't know why you thought
this was a good idea.
Couldn't have been easy to get here,
so I know you must want me back.
But having said that, if you
really value my happiness,
don't you have all this backwards?
Frankly,
you guys are poor and weak,
especially compared to the Big Mom Pirates,
who are generous enough to take me in.
So why would I ever choose you?
These are the big leagues.
You being king of the
pirates is a pipe dream.
It's only human nature
to pick the winning side.
You think this is funny, Sanji?
Nothing you're saying makes any sense!
So we were never really friends?
You were fooling me all this time?
That's right. Sorry.
Never thought much of you at all.
Did he just summon a flame? No way!
I'm glad we got Frontier seats to this
Is it hard to accept I imagine
you two didn't see this coming
Then I'll prove it to you
Get ready
Now Diablo Jamba
Shoo shot
Luffy's bleeding.
It can't be.
Is Sanji serious?
I said get ready.
If you don't use your Haki, you'll die.
What do I need Haki for?
I just want to talk to you.
Do what you want.
I won't fight.
You won't fight, then go away.
Not happening, you're stuck with me.
Selfish as usual, all right
then have it your way.
So listen, Mr.
Cook, why don't you leave
this boat and join my crew?
I could use a cook like
you on my pirate ship.
We don't want to fight, we want to help!
Don't you get it?
Lock fought all night against one of Big
Mom's strongest generals to get here.
He's in no shape to do this.
Nami, cut it out.
Stay out of this, okay?
It's between us.
We're having a duel.
Oh, that's what you think this is, huh?
Sanji, no!
Get out of my way!
Right!
I'm done with you!
That's enough!
Scram!
Beat it!
Go away!
I'm not leaving.
Oh, Lupi!
Don't do this!
Here we go.
How did this happen?
This is insane!
Please, Sanji, you don't
have to go through with this!
We'll go, just don't hurt Luffy!
I'm not leaving!
You're a good cook and I need one!
Obviously we should be pirates together!
Kunkasee!
What amazing strength!
I'd expect nothing less
if I've been smoke.
Please tell me you're
all right? Luffy! Luffy!
Come on, you gotta get up!
Say something to me!
Tell me you're okay!
Hey, Sanji!
Not so fast!
Now we're through.
I'm sorry.
Sorry we ever came here.
Aw, damn, that is so hot.
I like him, Feisty.
Their ties were meaningless.
Glad he severed them.
Thanks for waiting.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
Luffy!
Come back!
Sanji!
All your excuses sounded so fake!
I don't know why you said that
crap, but I know you didn't mean it!
You think that's going to make me leave?
Like we aren't friends?
A couple of dumb lies won't
make me give up on my crew.
What do you take me for?
I'm not stupid.
I know what's happening.
No matter how much you kick me,
you're the one who's getting hurt.
It's over.
Luffy, for some reason, Sanji's done.
Just shut up!
Should we stop?
He's still there.
Keep going.
By the way, have you ever
heard of the All-Blue?
That sea is a genuine miracle!
It has it all!
We're not done yet!
Our journey isn't over!
I'm staying right here and
I'm not moving an inch!
I'm gonna keep waiting
for you to come back!
And if you leave me here,
I'll just starve to death!
You're my chef!
No one else can take your place!
Sanji was making some
of that rat food again.
I'm not eating another bite of
anything unless you cook it!
Even if I get hungry,
even if spears or swords or stones break
down on me, I'll keep waiting for you!
you better come back you hear me no matter
what i need you on my
crew sanji without you
without you i'll never
be king of the pirates